'Cause I…
I can't see him
as just something to exterminate now.
You heard him.
[moans]
So why would we keep doing this?
I can't think of a reason.
[Knov] The King.
The soldiers are of no consequence.
The King can just wave his hand
and turn all of them into evil spawn.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
POSE X AND X NAME
Why do you and I have to fight?
Huh?
[King] You have absolutely
no chance of defeating me.
There is no need for us
to hasten your inevitable death.
[wind blowing]
Saying I can't win
is pretty presumptuous of you.
I can tell that you don't know
squat about me.
[blows]
If you judge a book by its cover,
don't be surprised if you get burned.
You don't seem like some ordinary man
who can't read the state of the battle.
Originally, you pathetic humans
were no more than livestock to me,
I have since determined
that there are a few humans
that are worth keeping alive.
Like that girl, for example.
You are worthy as well. I can sense it.
If you will back down this instant…
then I will consider sparing you.
[Netero] You're saying you would spare me
and not the others?
Is that right?
Given my unique position,
I simply can't accept that offer.
[suspense music playing]
[narrator] Meanwhile,
deep within the palace,
in exchange for his agreement
to stay still for the moment,
[sinister music playing]
and all that had transpired
since they had separated.
to ensure that Gon's attention
would be focused
on the explanation.
But Pitou, unable to describe
the events accurately,
There was no significant change in Gon.
[imperceptible]
The King…
he left with the enemy
of his own volition
by that doorway.
There's no need for us to go after him.
[Shaiapouf] Hmm.
I understand.
He went south.
Thank you for telling me.
A fine play, Pitou.
Then we should stay here
and await his return.
We must be patient.
The other segments will go…
to the King!
You will fight
knowing that you cannot win?
children may starve to death,
while on the left,
idle dregs who do nothing
have everything they need.
[Netero] Hmm.
[King] I don't deny that I'll start
by using power and terror
to accomplish my objective,
You see, I have learned
what true power is meant to be used for…
[imperceptible]
[King] …to protect the weak
who deserve to live.
That is its purpose.
Power shouldn't be used
to torment the defeated.
[suspense music playing]
yet it seems he hasn't yet realized
[somber music playing]
[man] We're counting on you.
You have only one mission to carry out,
the immediate execution of all
of these dangerous creatures.
Will that be acceptable to you?
Well, don't ask me.
We wouldn't dream of telling
the experts how to proceed.
Yes, of course. I understand.
Look, King…
we've all got problems, you know.
[gasps]
[ominous music playing]
[wind blowing]
[wings fluttering]
[gasps]
[Menthuthuyoupi] I can't sense
anyone else fighting here.
Does that mean
that I'm the only one left?
[Shaiapouf] Youpi!
[Menthuthuyoupi] Huh? Huh?
If I moved all my particles at once,
it would have been suspicious,
so I moved slowly.
I'm sure you're rushed,
but could you spare a moment?
Yeah. I suppose I've got a minute.
Guess everyone
does have their reasons.
[Shaiapouf] Uh…
You sound so grown up.
I hope Pitou's change
will benefit the King.
But I can't be sure.
I've no conclusive proof
one way or the other.
[sentimental music playing]
[narrator] Based on his own experiences,
Youpi could understand Pitou's behavior.
-[Shaiapouf] Youpi.
-[Menthuthuyoupi] Huh?
So tell me.
What do you think we should do now?
[narrator] He was being tested.
This tactic made it quite clear to Youpi
that Pouf was afraid,
unnerved by the subtle changes
[suspense music playing]
[Menthuthuyoupi]
There's no time to waste.
We must go to the King…
Indeed, you are.
[narrator] Only one thing
concerned him at the moment,
and that was leaving
as quickly as possible…
because the fear that gripped Pouf
had taken hold of Youpi as well.
[suspense music playing]
[spits]
[Netero] I'm sure that was a direct hit.
[King] A very good attack.
I wasn't expecting it.
[wind blowing]
Are you satisfied?
[Netero] Third hand!
I cannot back down any longer.
[gasps]
[creaking]
[ominous music playing]
[narrator] From the King's perspective,
the wrath that was unleashed
was unimpressive,
seemingly no stronger
than that of a child
throwing a tantrum.
But the King's full power
was violent enough
to make Netero jump back
more than twice his usual distance.
Netero couldn't help but feel insulted
by this turn of events
and by the fact that his determination,
strong as it was,
If it were that simple,
I wouldn't have to do this.
Wait.
Exchanging words?
How is it that you have come
into possession of my name?
Are you interested in fighting me now?
I'll make you a deal.
If you can force me to admit defeat,
So I'll be playing
without a rook and bishop.
[suspense music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[Gon] Next time,
"Centipede and Memory."
What do you want to be
in your next life?
[Killua] Uh, you first.
[Gon] In my next life, I wanna be me
so I can meet you again!
[singer singing in Japanese]